[
    {
        "prompt":"What is the collective noun for a group of crows?",
        "answer":"A Murder",
        "percentUnderstood":100,
        "nextView":0
    },

    {
        "prompt":"Which band's signature song is \"Wonderwall\"?",
        "answer":"Oasis",
        "percentUnderstood":10,
        "nextView":2
    },

    {
        "prompt":"What did a shepherd boy discover at Qumran, Jordan in 1946 and 1947?",
        "answer":"the Dead Sea Scrolls",
        "percentUnderstood":80,
        "nextView":1
    },
    
    {
        "prompt":"What type of mammals have pouches for carrying their young?",
        "answer":"Marsupials",
        "percentUnderstood":70,
        "nextView":3
    },

    {
        "prompt":"How many countries/regions are there in the United Kingdom? ",
        "answer":"4",
        "percentUnderstood":75,
        "nextView":4
    },

    {
        "prompt":"In computing, the term “bit” is an abbreviation of what?",
        "answer":"binary digit",
        "percentUnderstood":10,
        "nextView":5
    },

    {
        "prompt":"Darryl Philbin plays this character in Michael's fictional movie \"Threat Level Midnight\"",
        "answer":"the President of the United States",
        "percentUnderstood":0,
        "nextView":6
    },

    {
        "prompt":"Which Constitutional Amendment granted women the right to vote?",
        "answer":"the 19th Amendment",
        "percentUnderstood":15,
        "nextView":7
    },

    {
        "prompt":"What happens when a pig is struck by lightning?",
        "answer":"Turns into a Zombie Pigman",
        "percentUnderstood":100,
        "nextView":8
    },
    
    {
        "prompt":"Who was Americas first billionaire? ",
        "answer":"John D. Rockefeller",
        "percentUnderstood":25,
        "nextView":9
    }
]